Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat. N.
Hey,
hey, hey.
Hey.
Heat. Hey, Heat.
Uh hello. Wait, am I am I able?
Hello everyone. It's uh it's been
forever.
Hello. Uh one second.
I have to change my mic thingy in here.
Yeah, my PC is a whole mess.
Ah, it's a it's such a whole mess.
I haven't streamed in such a long time.
Uh, it's been 3 month 3 weeks already. I
about to say 3 months. Holy.
Um.
Okay. My PC is lagging. It's not
handling it.
Yeah. But it's not it's not handling it.
O.
Uh, give me a minute.
Uh, okay.
I think it's laggy. my audible.
Damn, it's hard to even stream. What
crazy?
Wait, am I not live? Wait, what?
Oh,
technical difficulties as always.
I missed uh when it comes to my setup
and everything. Uh it's such a
uh it's such a
in nutshell.
Okay. Um it's been a while. Uh so I
today I just wanted to like chat with
everyone.
um sad for 1 hour and then the next hour
I wanted to like do a study
uh session. Um
yeah, I'm super busy these days.
Uh I I'm super stressed
and
super uh like I been wanting to stream
so much but I'm unable to.
So, yeah, there's that. Is my stream
lagging? What the
crazy?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Ni.
Oh no,
my my PC is giving up on me. Yeah. Yeah.
the uh yeah um one of the reasons why I
wanted to stream but I couldn't was like
um
mainly like how tired I get every day
after like doing so much stuff
um yeah touching the rest life studies
preparations for uh since this is the
last month that a lot of things right in
my end And I want to stream but I can't
stream. But yeah, you know this week
whole week I was like okay I'm going to
stream though. I'm going to stream. Uh
Monday I was like I'm going to stream.
I'm going to just do a short 1 hour or
30 minute stream. Go back to uh like
revision and study stuff exam
preparations
and that never happened.
Tuesday. Same thing.
Yeah.
And uh it's like a rush hour moment this
whole month cuz I have to like speed run
a rush a lot of things. Get everything
done.
Yeah. Yeah. I have to like uh move
everything to the cloud. So many things.
My god, it's it's crazy. Honestly, it's
crazy.
Uh I don't know if my audio is good or
bad. Uh since uh yesterday
uh Elgato released an update for um uh
Wavelink 3.0,
like a stable version, full update. Um
and I lost my uh this thing, the whole
thing. I lost it. my whole back uh like
uh routing setup.
I lost it. I reseted it. So everything,
every intricate plugins, every single
thing I put is gone.
All my routings, everything go
Yeah, that that happened.
Show it.
I I was supposed to keep like a new chat
uh widget. You see the bottom run,
right? The one at the bottom. That's not
it. That was There's supposed to be
another one.
Um too much for my Mel studio.
Um yeah, my PC is dying, bro.
So, I'm supposed to be uh resetting my
PC like around uh next week.
Perhaps next week, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Next week. Uh yeah, I'm
going to be resetting
next week. Next Monday or Sunday. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. So, I'm like speedr
runninging a lot of uh uh backend
things.
Yeah. And also this stream uh in a way
one of the reasons for me to do this
stream was I needed some stuff to
uh do
um as in yeah multiple things. Uh yeah I
have some stuff I have to revise and
homeworkish. I won't be showing screen
basically. We'll be in this scene. We'll
have some um we'll have some low fight
music or same background music and I'll
I'll focus on studies and everything. As
I mentioned in my announcement a few
weeks ago, I'm just planning to just uh
do like steady stream or good uh just
chatting streams here and there.
Uh won't be too long
and won't be too short. So you can't
expit that.
So
there's that. Yeah.
Uh
on Jakand.
Uh one second. Let me double check
stuff.
My throat is bad doing bad. Oh my god.
Okay, it's been a while. So, I I forgot
how to stream. I know I'm supposed to
keep on talking, but yeah.
Oh, boy. It's been a while, hasn't it?
It has been a while.
And uh today after this stream actually
you might see a
page show up. Uh like I I
um this mean something I've been working
on like for the few days.
Uh you know me when it comes to stuff
about streams and everything I uh tend
to get this dev mode or something which
is bad. I uh
that's an intricate fellow like we uh I
go into deep deep about it. Uh one
second. Give me one second.
Okay, I'm back.
So, um,
what was I saying? My brain just uh
paused for a bit.
Yeah. Uh, so I've been doing some stuff.
Uh, when I when it comes to me, I go
into a long tangent.
Yeah. Stuff I'm interested about. If I
dabble into it, I go into a long t uh
long tangent.
So I've built like a archive system for
myself for uh myself and for viewers
um for all these past streams I have
done right. Um
I learned how to use
uh LLMs like AI stuff. Yeah. Yeah. how
to use an API endpoint to connect to an
uh uh a AI tool and let and let it do
the uh prompting and everything. Oh my
god, that was so nice. Yeah,
everything is automated.
Everything is now automated. I I don't
need to do much.
Uh it's nice honestly cuz uh for those
who don't know um I use Sammy a lot
right which needs a PC and needs to be
locally there like Sammy stream etc
right
but recently I discovered that you can
use uh like
so many new uh systems out there not new
systems But
um
how does it um
so many new um ways to
put your task out there and it it will
do it uh periodically on a schedule like
cloud for worker
GitHub actions also all the stuff.
So I made an archive page. Uh, if you
notice my sub account on Twitter, you
may have seen the link for a little bit
for approximately 4 hours and then I
deleted it. I was like testing my URL
stuff.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um, URL stuff and
everything. Why am I even yapping about
tech stuff? Oh my god.
Uh but yeah, it was really uh nice to do
it.
It was really nice to do it. Doesn't
hold much value or maybe it dash uh it's
just going to be like uh for all these
YouTube streams, right? Their transcript
will be there. The whole subtranscript
you see on YouTube as uh on YouTube, you
can see transcripts of videos and stuff,
right? Same thing that's going to be
here in the my website and there will be
chapters.
Haven't made them clickable and you can
watch the VOD from the website itself.
And then what else? And whenever there's
Billy Billy uh uploaded uploaded
uploaded archive of this like a specific
broadcast or a specific video page
you're looking at that will also have
that. So many things like that. Yeah, I
can I manually credit people as in
manually credit people as in um for
example stream assets I used uh if
anyone did any donations or subs,
follows etc. I could also thank
I could also thank them and put it put
it write it down manually and it'll show
up.
Yeah, I I the stuff
and today stream after stream I'm going
to be probably linking Twitch chat. So
Twitch chat is going to be there. Yeah,
YouTube channel is going to be there by
the way.
Yeah, there's so many things I've been
doing, I guess. Kind of unnecessary uh
but more in the backend side cuz again I
uh would love it as a oneman show uh as
I myself is there uh I can't uh do stuff
as I used to do. I just want to hop in,
do my thing and get off. Right. So these
all back and stuff uh helps to like
um scheduleize everything so I don't
need to do much. Really good system
show.
Wait. Uh did the announcement on Discord
fire out? Let me check. I'm sorry if I'm
lagging. My PC is not
doing the best.
Um, give me a minute.
Am I alive?
Mh.
M mate. Uh,
it's not a shame that I'm wonder
Oh, I forgot to take my bottle. Ah,
what?
I forgot to take my bottle. Ah.
Now to go. No.
Okay, give me a minute. Um,
hold up.
Hold your shoes, everyone.
Uh, one shot.
Mhm.
And uh
yeploy this as well.
And
it should be good. Uh the announcement
should be made by now. Yeah.
Let me see the action
next. Did it send a ping?
Bro, this is broken.
This is rocky.
Message mentions exclusive parts lower.
What the What the heck?
No.
Coding
meni.
Oh my god.
Uh, anyway, I'll get my bottle from
downstairs. Give me a minute. Uh,
I really hate to do this. Uh, I don't
want to be away from stream. It's very
stream.
I'm just 24 minutes in.
Oh my god,
man.
Oh my god. I I just started. Oh. Uh, one
second. Give me a minute.
He stopped working. So, I've been
sweating like a
boiled egg.
God, why is the species so laggy? What
happened to you?
Uh, okay. I'll be back in a bit. Uh, do
I have any BRB thingy? Um,
I don't think so. But do I have anything
here?
God, I'm so unprepared.
Love it.
Uh
BRBing
water.
Okay, we are everyone.
Hi
Okay, I'm here. I'm here.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
Uh,
yeah, I'm back. Hello. Hello.
I can remove that.
All right,
I got my tea.
You know, I didn't know today was holy
and until I saw some neighbors like
throwing colors outside.
H time is going by so quickly, huh?
You never notice it when you're like
fully indulged into um a lot of things
and you forget how goes by so quickly.
And it's already March.
Isn't that crazy?
It's already March though.
Already
March. Wait one second. Um you know
what? Um,
I'll I'll talk in the background. I'll
just uh do work stuff and
yeah,
I'll do work stuff.
Need to do something about my PC stuff
though. Like literally though, like
uh it do be lucky.
The PC bottleneck is crazy.
Think I can close this.
Yeah, my current setup um
it's good I know but
yeah
I I anyways will be like purging
everything
I have to clean up whole thing
system wise
and cloud back up a lot of things. Oh
god, I'm I'm posted. I have to do it
before a week.
Okay, let me just quickly just do these
stuff and get back into
um steady show. I guess it's 30 minutes,
right? Yeah. Yeah, it's it's fine. I can
um make most of the time today.
just
shut their off. Oh, I didn't know tw Oh,
I feel gone.
I do not announce on Instagram that I'm
live.
Oh wait. Um
I actually forgot. Wait.
Oh wait. How am I?
No,
I forgot to announce.
Oh, wait. I can just go to GitHub and
just download my thumbnail. I put that
main stuff, right? Oh, yeah. But it's a
hectic to find my thumbnail.
Ah,
the video already not.
Okay, so I wanted to put like a mother
timer kind of thingy while I'm studying
while I do my steady stuff today.
Yeah.
Um,
what can I do?
Okay, just uh quickly do the
let me just quickly do the thing and uh
start
Instagram.
I think Instagram is the only thing
which is left for me to like
Uh
yeah, that's the only thing which is
left for me to like
literally uh automate in some way.
Oh, apparently you can't Oh, wait.
Yeah, that's stupid thing.
I would love it if I could actually do
it. Anyway,
I'm gonna fix my Discord thingy.
Uh,
I want to fix my disc so I can like
do it.
Okay.
Uh,
you know, when you're a PNG, you don't
see much movement, right?
Well, I got to get used to it.
The thing with me is like uh I I keep
thinking uh that I'm using a live 3D
model and I keep moving my head around.
Uh so it captures the expression and I
realize I'm still I'm a PNG now. So that
doesn't matter anymore.
By the way, they did you know there's
this um
um new application which came out like
uh two weeks ago on Twitter
uh called um what's it called again?
Face to
face to
face to something. So you can uh use
your facial expressions actually to
trigger stuff for your emote uh like for
your model and stuff which is actually
nice.
That is actually cool actually.
So
that is nice.
Um, wait.
Let me let me tweet.
One sec.
Life from the void.
It's
a while happy.
Okay. Hi, Twitter. I mean, uh TW um
Instagrammed.
Okay. Uh
where is the Discord
engines?
Let me just fix it. You know, apparently
a lot of people have been moving away
from
Discord recently.
It's crazy.
Oh my god.
Uh, I had thoughts about it.
I had thoughts about it. Then I'm like,
a thought came across me. Okay.
It's like
okay if I'm moving to a different
platform what am I going to do with all
these 3 4 months worth of work I did uh
automating my uh full Discord stuff. So
when I'm live it it does everything for
me. When I'm not live it does everything
for me. When I uh
when I like make an update on my website
it does stuff for me in the behind the
scenes. gives me a receipt uh makes the
receipts for me
uh uh on during any uh payouts and
stuff. YouTube judge, I made that stuff
as well. Connected that to a thingy in
this private server thingy. A lot of
things I did so I can go. It's all going
to be
thrown in the dumpster
if I were to like move away
from this code.
Yeah. Plus the chat log system, right?
Oh yeah.
Uh five years worth of chat logs of
everyone in this channel on YouTube
stretch.
Holy, I'm going to miss that.
But hey, if if it was possible though
to um if it was possible though to like
um
uh what do you call it? If it was
possible to actually
somehow scrape that data off.
Oh my god, that's going to be so good.
That's going to be so nice.
Why am I nodding? Hello. Hello.
How are you? I missed you and it's been
a while I streamed.
Thank you for coming by.
Fore!
Foreign! Foreign!
I
hi.
Um
Gy kind of
like um
No. Uh
uh. Uh
Yeah.
Preparation.
Oh my god.
Then there's
Hi
Um
um
uh
um like work stuff is basically stream
stuff.
Uh,
so
like
um
Um
obvious
control
local like
uh
in
Oh my god. Wait, a go there. Oh my god.
I'll to say it in English.
So um for uh doing live streams not like
this stream etc.
I have so many applications
which uh runs in the computer not in my
computer
uh so it can um run stuff automatically.
So I don't know they need to do stuff.
No
automation
there's no
automation.
Hi uh if I uh next month when I'm
leaving
so I don't have PC I won't be taking PC
right to Japan. So I moved it to cloud
cloud
automation
show
there
cloud.
Uh
yeah. So
GitHub,
GitHub action
cloud workpe.
Um
Becky. Wait, why am I using Becky here?
Yeah.
Hello, Kaneki. Hello. Hello. Happy holy.
Welcome.
I'm looking for the time you move back
to Japanese. Yeah. Yes. Yes. Yes. Next
month.
Excited.
So, yeah. Basically, I've been uh moving
all of my stuff to cloud.
Uh
yeah,
we're moving everything to cloud. Sorry.
Uh we don't celebrate holiday. Okay.
Okay. One second.
Wait. Uh, oh yeah, I don't celebrate it.
But
wait, so people wish on Holly, right?
How come you stream today? It's a long
story.
Um,
lately I've been wanting to stream every
single day. I was like, I want to stream
Hinste
I want to stream. I want to stream
everything. I've been saying, but um I
was like, if I'm too tired and dead
inside, what's the point in streaming?
I'm supposed to talk and entertain all
those stuff, even though I'm having a
really busy schedule with everything
going on uh this month, right? I have to
speedrun everything. Um, yeah. So,
uh, yeah, I was like,
uh, in the middle of, uh, like wipe
coding my stuff recently, uh, for my
stream, more like a, uh, archive system
for all of my YouTube streams. No.
Uh, yeah. Yeah. So I was like, "Oh, I
have to connect Twitch uh Twitch data
into a YouTube uh ID, right?" So I was
like, "Okay, I'm going to do a stream
today. Uh I can't link my 20 the the
always on 24x7 channel data to my main
YouTube stuff, right?" So I was like,
"Okay, I'm going to do a stream today.
After a stream, I'll just uh do my stuff
and like automatically link Twitch and
YouTube chat together and people can go
to my website, see the archive stream of
this broadcast and they can read the
chat, who all came, who all talked, etc.
It was it's useless, but still I was
wanted to do it. Yeah. And recently I
was like uh wanting to stream but uh
yeah what do you call it PC stuff not
happening. PC was like sometimes not
even turning on. I prayed a lot and
today it turned on. Yeah. So my 24
channel run somehow. But yes.
Hello A. Hello. Hello.
Good evening.
How's everything? Um,
yeah, preparations are going. I bought a
new bag.
My tech um I call it my tech baggie. Uh,
it's a American tourist bag. Uh, it has
a USB plug. Um, yeah, it has a USB plug
on the on the um side. I can put a power
bank and like I can charge my phone,
other equipment and stuff. So, go. It's
really good actually.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And um what else? Um
um I've been deciding what all stuff I
need to take in my luggage or in my tech
baggie which I just mentioned. Like I
have to take my gooseeneck mic arm a
gooseeneck phone stand which I used for
my phone tracking back in the days. I
bought that. I have to take that. Of
course, I have to take my MIDI keyboard.
I have to take my uh phone uh my
wireless mics uh wireless mic. And I'm
still debating if I should take my this
mic I'm using for stream
or uh abandon both of them
and buy it from there. Who knows? I
don't know. Uh but again, there's the
weight limit now. So I'm I'm like uh
thinking uh what I what do I do? How to
get everything in?
There's that.
And uh yeah, preparations are going
every day. My my uh every day I'm
getting called by family to go to the
bank here, here, here, sign this
document, this and that. I have to file
my GST this month. I haven't been filing
my GST stuff for Jockn uh for the past
four months. I have to talk with the
incand people and like be like yeah I'm
not earning much so can you auto do this
for me and I have to also do my um
YouTube uh payout the I have to talk
with my bank to auto make it so that I
don't have to come in person to seal
uh to seal the documents
whenever I'm having a YouTube payout
uh cuz my bank will hold the money you
No. So I have to do that. Even though I
made like an automated system where it
sends to my discord like whenever I get
like a YouTube payout thingy, it uh
checks the am the amount and
automatically gives me a template for
the
uh invoice. I have a invoice system. I
finally made an invoice.
So it'll give the uh invoice stuff. So I
can just copy paste it and in the p uh
the PDF editor now. Yeah. Yeah. And I
can easily uh just make some changes and
I can easily um like seal it and give it
to the bank so they can approve my funds
which are in pending all those stuff.
Yeah, I did that long ago.
Out of nowhere I was like this is so
dumb. Why do I have to make my own
invoice even though I'm a business? But
still, wow.
So, I I have to do like 00001 00002.
Cool. The show. Yeah. In the future, if
we have merchandise or something, I'm
going to use that invoice system to
generate invoice for people who are
buying merch or something.
Oh, yeah. It is nice. I did so much
stuff.
I went into a I went into a tangent.
Ah, nice. I think I'll buy it, too. I'm
not sure.
GST. Yeah, I uh So, I uh in order to
hide my real name when you do UPI trans
uh uh don transactions, right? I I have
a UPR link in the description if you if
you want to check it. It show gives you
the IED. So yeah, in order to hide it, I
had to in India, you have to become a
business sole proprietor at least
and make a bank current account in your
channel name. So you can like hide your
real name when pay people pay you money
or something through UPI upon your
second channel. Ah thank you
Joitch
for
uh channel.
What the I made. It's not fully done,
but you can see it, I guess.
Wait, this is today's live stream.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Wait. M. So, uh,
uh, this is also
this is also
archive page that I've been working on.
What that
a new archive page I've been working on.
It has
it's uh not fully
done yet. Uh
but
has uh AI some chapters
and uh YouTube live chat
and
transcripts etc.
Got it.
Where you going? Merch coming when? Uh
I'm not sure about that.
Uh
a merch thing is uh hit mess. It's hard.
How to find a company which will
actually take you in and help you with
stuff. It's hard though in this day and
age.
You have to be a bigger brand or
whatever. No,
but I wish I could.
Not coming soon. No, no, no. It maybe in
the far future though. Maybe there's a
chance.
Yeah, maybe there's a chance. Yes.
What's uh today? Uh, I just wanted to
chat with everyone. Maybe it's been a
while now. I I haven't streamed for 3
weeks. Um, just wanted to chat. Uh, and
and
in like uh 5 minutes from now, I'll just
go to my do study stuff. I'll be here.
It's just going to be studying, doing
homework, Japanese stuff I have. Uh, so
it's going to be a steady. It will
transition from a a talking stream to um
steady thing.
Yeah,
my whole setup is all uh
um messed up since I haven't streamed
now.
Um
uh it should just one second. It should.
But yeah, wait. Sorry. H I was like, my
brain lagged.
My multitasking is hard. I'm trying to
fix the discard thingy.
I have a placement test to give right
now. And by the way, I have a visa
application now. I'm super scared. Oh my
god.
Um uh
for me uh they said I have to pay the
stuff by 7th.
Yeah. But before Saturday
I have to do the payment stuff.
I don't know what's next. I I think I
will also have an entrance exam.
I just hope I'm not confident in my N4
level yet. Even though I've been I I can
revise and catch up to it easily, but
still I I'm not that confidentish at the
moment kind of. So, um I I I I would
love it if they could put me in entry
if if possible. I would be happy.
But if not possible, it's
understandable.
Yeah, it's understandable.
But but I'll I'll probably be put in for
I have to grind my way up.
Da
da.
I have an accident that I did. Oh, wait.
Did you clear N4?
Did you clear N4? Did you pass it?
That's crazy.
Oh my god.
Uh,
excuse me.
okay. Close this.
Uh
no, I'm at base of info. Okay. Okay.
Okay. And base. No. Okay. Okay. So,
grammar, right? Um potential form,
passive form,
all those stuff, right?
Base.
Yes. Happy holy. I don't though I don't
celebrate it. But happy holy.
Happy holy.
My PC is lagging.
Am I live? Okay, I'm live. Okay. Okay,
it froze for a second.
Uh, you better stream at least. Oh,
wait. Wait. Auto mode. No. So, wait.
Your message got auto mode. Uh, you
better stream at least twice a week.
I'll try. I'll try. Kind of kiss.
Expired and not posted to chat. What?
Wow. Thank you for the hydrate reminder.
Thank you.
A nonashi.
Oh, my voice sounds weird today.
I'm going to do this.
Hello from Twitch.
Hello. Thank you for dropping by on
Twitch. Hello. Oh, yeah. Speaking of
Twitch, uh uh Twitch changed the
multistreaming rules now. Uh apparently
I can finally uh show YouTube and Twitch
kick comments
openly on stream. I don't need to
separate it.
Thank you Dan Clansancy for changing uh
the roles stuff. He he
thank you for reminder.
Uh,
not bad.
Oh, one second. I'm listed.
Huh?
Since your board patches the message
repeating, this code could re-trigger
mentions if you're not careful. Save me
by
which is awesome.
Uh, okay. Deploy.
Okay. Trigger.
Come on. Work for me.
Okay. Refresh. And uh it should trigger.
Oh, uh smile check. Oh, smile check is
basically a community uh goal you can
say. Basically, if you have spare
channel points, right, you can just
contribute it to a goal. Smile check is
basically like
um
how do I say it's like
uh hi how are you? I hope you're having
a good day. Hope you hope you're smiling
today kind of thingy. Yeah,
that's what I was wanting to go for.
Yeah.
Wait, why is it using Q HQ?
No, that's bad. Okay, wait.
You donated all the point.
Nice.
Okay.
One second.
It It feels weird when I'm
not showing what I'm doing, but also you
get me a corporate role ID.
It's too technical, I think.
Yeah.
I don't want to bore bore people with
this. Yeah. Okay, let me copy paste
this. Deploy.
It's using an
480p quality thumbnail. Why?
Huh? Weird. That's so weird, man.
Open in browser. HQ quality. High
quality default
live.png.
No.
H.
That's weird.
I can't
like I'm done with messing around with
the API stuff and the automated stuff
for stream. Everything is going well
if I'm correct. Automatically detects
when I'm live. All my uh automations are
running. Uh I need to keep the timing
more frequent I guess. Yeah. And um
so far it's going doing great I guess.
Yeah. If you guys have any ideas now
regarding my website stuff or anything
like that do uh tell me. I would love
I'm open for suggestions. Okay. I would
really love that.
Yeah,
you know uh
of coding is crazy
like in Sammy it took me
3 weeks or more to set up make all these
uh structured intricate highly detailed
setup
and with coding even though I know I
don't know coding but I wipe uh like use
chip to code and stuff. It only took me
like few 50 to 100 lines of code to
recreate what I did in three to four
weeks in Sami. Crazy.
Oh my god. And I'm like, man,
insane.
Oh, money. What is this way?
Oh. Oh my god.
Thank you for subbing. You don't have
to. Oh my god. You don't have to. Wait.
Isn't Twitch expensive?
Thank you for subscribing. O. Don't
subscribe on Twitch.
You don't have to. You don't have to.
Actually, Twitch takes so much money.
Twitch will take half of it.
Yeah. Oh my god. They were from YouTube
though. But but still I appreciate it so
much. Thank you.
But save your money.
Yeah.
Shave your okane.
Save your okane.
Save the okane.
Um,
isn't there a song?
What's up? Or something. And now I can't
change the price sadly. Twitch Twitch be
Twitch be like that.
Uh Twitchy Twitchy be like that.
Oh, there's no Max R quality for this
thumbnail. Oh, that's why. Oh,
yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That song. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That song.
Yes. Yes.
Yes.
really nice song though.
Mhm.
Man, so many streaming gear has beena
has came out this year 2026 and I'm like
man if I had okane
I could buy it.
Uh Salt says an ad. You don't see it
because you are a subscriber. If you pay
for Twitch subscriber,
uh you don't see ads. It's ad free.
Yeah.
Adree viewing. You don't see ads.
You don't see ads. Just like YouTube
Premium.
So
just to like YouTube Premium
speaking of YouTube Premium, you know,
uh yeah, recently uh uh YouTube Premium
gave like a new right premium light or
something.
Apparently, if you didn't know,
Workspace accounts, Google Workspace
accounts are not able to buy uh you
can't use Workspace accounts
uh to buy Google products like Google
one, Google, yeah, YouTube Premium, etc.
But I was I was somehow able to buy
YouTube Premium Premium on my uh
Workspace account. So I can finally
I can finally use my jocks account to
uh like yeah enjoy YouTube premium stuff
again.
So like I used to use my Gmail account
and added my YouTube channel as a uh
like a what do you call it manager or
something so I can use premium when I
switch to jockn account on YouTube right
since I needed like more YouTube access.
I need more YouTube permission access.
Apparently, I discovered you could
somehow
only buy YouTube Premium from desktop
from from the browser for your um
workspace account and it somehow works.
Yeah. Yeah. Back in the days, uh you uh
you can't do that. Apparently Google
doesn't like when people like um people
buy uh their products from
what do you call it? Buy products from
their thing. I I don't get it. But yeah.
Yeah. Uh if you are a uh um workspace
account, no, you can't buy Google one
etc. workspace have a different storage
plan thingy.
Yeah,
it's kind of weird, but yeah, but I'm at
least happy I can like do that. And I
have to uh put the student plan for
premium. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I can do it
from the language school. Apparently, I
checked my language school. It is there
in the YouTube and I put the country as
Japan. So I can benefit from it. I just
need to upload my ID card or something.
If I when I get it, I can enjoy premium
for a cheaper price.
So the
by
papa.
being the wrong
Miami life.
I was wondering why bit what is bits and
why not and it shows 195 for one bits.
Wait, what?
Wait, did they increase the price for
bits? Wait, what?
Wait, one. No. One one 138 rupees 400
bits. Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's crazy.
100 much money. Oop.
The thing is not Twitch's chatting
experience is nice.
like super fast interactiveness,
channel points, uh watch streak bonus,
etc. integrations, API stuff, etc. Those
are good when it comes to Twitch.
But rest of the things like ads,
all these uh stuff, they uh squeeze
money out of streamers. That's a crazy
thing.
Yeah.
It is all pain.
Uh YouTube is doing so many things now.
The YouTube CEO is
doing so many new things and this is
cool.
I I'm not so that active on Twitter to
consume like uh these announcements and
news stuff.
I sometimes happen to see them and I um
I'm like okay. Oh, this is happening in
the world right now. All right. Like
that.
Um,
all that stuff.
Oh, yeah. Uh, there is this um
there is this new VTuber database
website I saw on Twitter today.
Uh uh yeah, apparently my 24x7 channel
is there.
Yeah, crazy though.
Uh wait, let me let me show you one
second.
Um
hello Kellyan. Hello. Hello. Hello.
Wild Sashi booty.
booting
machine.
Uh,
wait.
How do I do this? I forgot. Uh, oh yeah.
Yeah, this is how I do it. So, there's
this website called Barach. But, this is
Indonesian. Uh, this translates to
Vtuber database. So it this project uh
this website uh fetches data from fandom
vtuber fandom wiki a hollow list uh
vtuby etc. Okay. So, if I go to browse
tubers here and type jo
why why oh wait sorry spelling mistake
you see both my accounts why why is my
always on channel here why how n
why is this channel here crazy
uh yeah for uh like language hind Hindi
uh I show up first for some reason but
other YouTubers are here. So yeah this
uh this data
my VTuber wiki page from fandom. I
believe it took data from here
which I need to update a lot of things.
I have to remove update this right.
Yeah I have to update my stuff. Oh yeah,
it shows like okay this is not updated
but last tweet when was my last tweet.
So they pay for X uh X API or something
and they fetch the latest tweets or are
they crawling this? Wow. Wait, it all
shows that I'm live over here. Crazy.
Yeah, all the stuff is not bad.
Uh,
wait. What is Ah, yeah. I have to remove
the collaborations. Yeah, to remove
that. Yep. Yep.
I I love this thingy. They have the
sections here. Nice.
Why is YouTube not there?
Weird.
H I have to like uh make my own version
of this in my website.
Also, I'll show you my my recent stuff I
made uh which is the archives page. I'm
going to add uh so many metadata and SEO
stuff later. So, this was my last
stream, right? February 4th. Was this
Valentine's Day? Wait, I never I I
didn't stream on Valentine's Day. So,
yeah. Here at this page, you can watch
the archive. You can watch the archive
if you want. They'll be Billy as well if
the video is uploaded to Billy. Then
broadcast details. When did it start? Uh
when the live stream Yeah. when the live
stream was scheduled. Well, let me can I
zoom this in? Hello. Uh
it might be too much for Oh god. Yeah.
Uh the stream description from YouTube.
Stream transcripts. Yeah, I got this D.
Look, it fetches the whole transcripts.
the whole thing
from YouTube.
So, and uh you see yourself as well you
for YouTube people. Twitch people. After
today's stream, I'm going to integrate
Twitch chat here as well.
So, yeah. So, this has all the Twitch uh
YouTube data. Uh if when people came by
to my stream now, like who who all came
by their chats, you can publicly Yeah.
way you're here can publicly view that.
Really nice
and stream summary. Uh this one uh I'm
going to change the name to my words
like dogs stuff or something. Chapters
is AI based. So this transcripts right
this subtitles like SRT stuff from
YouTube stream that gets sent to AI and
AI turn gives me this AI chapterish
and AI summary as well. This going to be
up top maybe or below here. I have to
work on that. So yeah
stream goals is something these are
manual entries. Uh if I have to show an
example um
if I have to show an example it will be
like a manual entry I have to fix the
yeah there will be stream goals stream
review additional roles uh notes and
stuff in the future I'm planning to add
like contributions
uh stream contributions that means if
anyone followed me during a specific
stream
uh followed me or send sub like data
subscription like Twitch subs, YouTube
membership, etc. Those will be manually
uh mentioned here kind of thing. Here
you go. Yeah. Yeah. Stream review is
about me. I'll manually write this on
notion like how many times my stream
broke, any audio issues I need to keep
note of or something.
uh stream goals is basically what are
the goals I did for the specific stream?
What are the things we have to do and
did I was I able to achieve it or not
like that.
Yeah.
Cool. the show
and in the future I'll add um chatbased
reminder system here like we have the
thing right where it shows up on uh h
sorry where it shows up on uh my discord
server when someone does a reminder
command exclamation remind joke
and you add the message right so um
basically that off. I'm going to put it
in the websh. One second.
>> Where is it?
>> Uh,
what is it? Yeah. Yeah, this thing. This
thing. Got it.
Yeah. Remind doc, right? Twitch chat
reminder. YouTube chat reminder. So,
we'll have a reminder section up here.
So, yeah. Yeah. If you have any
reminders, for example, you suggested me
a game I could play in the future
streams. Yeah. Yeah. I can note it down.
Not only limited to Discord now, it will
be on the side. Cool. The show.
Yeah. Then if I forgot about it, I can
just come back here or something and or
I I can have like a search bar here and
I can search maybe and it will show up
show show me the stream, right? Yeah.
Really will it will be really nice. God,
I'm I'm I'm like over engineering right
now.
Why?
Why is there a PFP of jox7 so manly? Oh,
this that was a old fan art from a
artist. Yeah. Yeah. I'm probably going
to be updating all my channel um BFPs
and everything
for when I get my new model stuff and
it's out.
I I thought of um doing the new model
reveal um some someday around this year.
Not sure when. I'll let you guys know.
So,
I'll let you guys know.
Oh,
let me drink some water. Thank you for
the hydrate reminder. Everyone do
hydrate as well.
Wait, it would be so nice if if it can
log channel redeems like this. So, I can
keep count. I can keep count how many
times uh people have used channel points
and stuff.
So
that will be so nice.
Yeah.
Um
Do you want to see I don't know if I
should show this publicly,
but you want to see uh some backend
stuff.
Um
backend stuff I did recently, man. Let
me show you.
One second.
Okay, you want to see some backend
stuff? I know it's boring but still
wait.
So backend stuff. Let's start with
GitHub. So this is my Jocknik YouTube
data. Basically a YouTube archiver. So
this consists of the AI AI summaries you
saw before, right? For each video there
will be a summary the chapters all the
chapters for the video and the summary
of what this uh summary was about what
the stream was about. That's the AI
folder and the live chat folder will
have the
uh yeah live chat which is this is a row
live chat uh and this is the normalized
version which is this is what you see on
the website
and um
there is subtitles. Yep, subtitles is
also there. Uh I have English original,
English, Japanese and Chinese and
Chinese simplified as well. So uh yeah,
English uh SRT will look like this.
Normal SRT thingy supports video editors
as well. VTT for this one. And the JSON
file is actually used for uh my website.
Yeah. Yeah. JSON file. And I have a
timeline system which is this. Timeline
is like it shows chat with the
subtitles. See this? So uh how can I
yeah shows chat
and the uh yeah so type sorry subtitle
type chat like that it will show then I
have a chunk thingy cuz subtitles and
chats are if I'm doing a 12-hour stream
and if it has like uh so many chats so
many uh uh like subtitles right I have
to get the chunks like little bits of
data right. So, this has around 200
chunks, I believe, or 150 chunks. One
chunk looks like this. A little small
bites of data. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And uh thumbnail thingy. Each stream.
Oh, wait. Where's the thumbnail? Thumb.
Uh yeah, there's a thumbnail folder. It
has all 1,70
streams I have done on YouTube.
Uh, and it gives me the hash
uh B 64 of the thumbnail like of a
specific thumbnail like this like
thumbnail. And this is in JPA JPG
format. Yeah. So less MP not PNG. Yeah.
Comes from YouTube by the way. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like that. And I I
will like this thing. I have like
workers which does everything
automatically.
Uh this is the discord one basically
what um basically it automatically
automates my
uh events. Same thing I did events and
uh announcements
stuff and schedules is now active. We
have schedule system now and this shows
private streams private unlisted. I have
to change this. So you have you can
actually see the status like cancelled.
Yeah, don't mind this. Unknown. Yeah,
some streams are cancelled. Yeah, all
those stuff. The streams are cancelled,
streams are delayed, postponed, haven't
even streamed through. All the private
data will be here. Yeah, that's the
Discord stuff.
Then V engine is basically my YouTube V
system, right? The website stuff. Uh I
think at this point I can show
everything.
Why not?
So I have a V system, right? This is my
back end for my whole uh YouTube V
thingy, right? If you never knew. Uh oh
my god, it's laggy. Yeah, this is how my
channel stuff works. 90 videos, right? I
made I got inspiration from
I got inspiration. Oh my god, my stream
is lagging. I got inspiration from Asmin
goals 24x7 channel. I I finally made a
canvas system. Wait, wait, wait. Let me
close it. I made a canvas system. So, uh
player will be shrink. There's a
schedule which all the uh playlist going
to be played.
Uh yeah, it works real time. So if I
switch to Hongkey star rail, it'll go
number five. I need to fix this. But
yeah,
yeah, canvas system is work in progress.
I have to move this to cloud. Um, still
using Sammy to do this locally. I have
to switch to Cloudfare.
Then what else? Uh
yeah archiver is uh data which gets from
the GitHub automatically
and um and then what then what uh notion
gateway is literally a parser worker I
made and uh jon stream API this is how
my live stream archive page is running
so it uses this website uh API/all all.
So, it gets all my YouTube streams, all
uh all of my YouTube stream data. Same
thing I did on uh Savvy, I switched it
into cloud, description, thumbnail,
embed, every single thing, the Discord
announcement stuff, event stuff. Yeah.
Yeah. So, my idea is Oh, yeah. I forgot
to show you one more thing. Twitch for
people on Twitch. I didn't forget you.
So I made it so that it will have a
archive. Currently it logs my 24x7
channel. So it will have a list of data
like uh the meta data. Uh when did the
stream start, thumbnail channel, all
those stuff
and uh I have the chat row the row chat.
So all the people on Twitch even the
bots channel points everything will be
here probably
and chat normalized is the website uh
readable version. So users will be here.
Uh then basically I can did I close my
website? I did. Oh so basically I can
like um
uh live stream archives. Basically I can
put YouTube chat no Twitch chat here.
Hello.
Hello. Hello. It's been a while. Happy
holy. Wait, why is it not loading? So, I
can basically put Twitch chat up here as
well. Yeah. Yeah. I want to get like a
mer chat. Both YouTube and Twitch should
show up here in one uh thingy.
Did you program all of this by yourself?
Nah, I use chip code. It is. You think I
know coding? I don't know coding now.
If I knew coding, I could have done so
much things. I I would have made my own
Discord stuff. I would have made so many
things though.
Yeah.
What is this? Did it break? Yeah, I
think this is broken. Not sure what was
that.
Uh, so yeah, really nice. No, like an
archive thingy section. You can just see
it. M. And this works on um
this this will be a a good way for me to
post my ending um tweet or something on
Twitter. So if I were to copy this, if I
were to copy this and make a tweet or
something, right? If I were to p
if I were to post something like this,
right? If I had to post something like
this.
Uh, wait. Where is it? Oh, yeah. It
shows the meta data. It uses the summary
card. Large shows the title. Shows
jocknik archive. So, I just can be like,
yeah, it's a stream. It's a stream
summary for today. It was a fun stream.
Yeah, I can just type less, put the
link, people click on the link,
they can read transcripts,
read stuff, etc. Easy.
More convenient if you ask me.
Show that.
Yeah,
everything is automated, so I don't need
to worry touch anything.
Isn't it cool?
This was an idea which I got like uh uh
uh 3 days ago and I started to like
speedrun do this.
Uh
so
very cool.
Yeah.
though
really nice actually cuz again no when I
don't have PC with me when I'm leaving
next month
um everything will be broken everything
will be messed up even if I go live on
my phone on YouTube app things will not
work the same right
now I don't need to worry every 1 hour
or two or a weekly I have a schedule for
running all these automations and like I
can just do my stream from anywhere like
Twitch. Oh no no mainly YouTube. Yeah
mainly YouTube PC stream or mobile
stream whatever it will automate
everything. Yeah I just have to do the
uh sadly I have to do the tweet
Instagram story. Yeah.
Why am I saying sadly?
Cool. The show. So I I don't need to
worry about stuff.
God
uh
uh this is about 25 overall. Overall
overall Yeah. Yeah. Overall 24x channel.
I haven't uh I have to uh move that to
um Cloudfare
and like make it automated. I haven't
done it yet. I have to do that.
Um I have to do that. Sure.
I was thinking of doing it tomorrow, day
after.
I have to also reset my whole PC now cuz
it's like fully clogged up. So many
stuff I have to uninstall. So many
games.
Wow. So many things.
Wow.
Yeah. But mainly is for all actually. I
mean 24x7 stuff. Uh it's done actually.
I don't need to do much, right?
Like um 24x stuff.
uh 24x7 and stuff. All I have to do is
open OBS and just uh
put this website link, put this website
link, it will automatically refresh the
browser every Saturday. If you're
watching the VOD, like say you're just
watching a video here, okay, from the
website directly or from YouTube,
Twitch, any platform, it will
automatically refresh the page for you.
Yeah. I made I made it so that it will
automatically refresh at 12:00 a.m. on a
Saturday. That's when the new um
playlist gets refreshed, right? Yeah.
Yeah. So, uh this week's playlist is
Poppy Playtime, Final Fantasy, Hongkey
Star real, uh Battle Bet Remastered, and
everything is random. Yeah, everything
is random.
So
really nice if you ask me.
Kind of glad I did all of this cuz every
time I stream now I I used to feel super
overwhelmed like man
why did I do this in the first place?
Why am I suffering?
And and now I don't need to suffer much.
It ease to my suffering.
I I used to get frustrated when things
doesn't work the way I wanted. They said
that uh yeah
plus the archive page is mainly for
public
those who do don't have access to
YouTube like for example the Billy Billy
audience right who can't watch YouTube
Twitch kick all of this the all of those
sites are banned in China right so they
can at least uh check my website see the
stream I did see uh like metadata Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. It spins. Yes.
The transition.
So yeah,
it does spin
the spinnies.
The spinnies. Yep. Yep.
Spin finish
maning is crazy man. Honestly speaking
so many things every every month there's
something.
Yeah.
But honestly speaking, I I realized one
thing which keeps keeps me wanting to
be a YouTuber
regardless of what's happening all
around me. It's just that I am
really into the YouTuber concerts and
like all the tech behind that,
right?
And every time I watch concerts by
VTuber like VTuber concerts,
um,
etc.
It inspires me to like one day do the
same someday, you know.
It's really nice.
What's the control thingy on the top
left corner? Control thingy. What? What?
What? What?
H.
Which one? Oh, if you see number like ad
uh three, one out of three, that's
Twitch ad stuff.
Yeah, that's only for Twitch people.
When there is a Twitch ad running, uh I
have a overlay which shows that yeah,
there's a ad running kind of thingy.
So many things.
So many things though.
Control. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Twitch. Oh.
Okay. Okay. Control. Uh stream kit is
um
it's an extension
on Twitch. If I'm correct,
control plus is a extension on Twitch. I
believe I set this up long back. I
forgot about it. So, you can provide
information
FAQ and stuff.
Uh, this is like a Twitch extension.
Yeah, there are other extensions where
you can bonk the streamer with a hammer
when you're watching them or like um uh
trigger sound effects when you click on
the play video player. There's so many
things like that. Those are all Twitch
extensions.
The one you are seeing is an overlay
extension
and ones at the bottom like uh if you
scroll down you see like uh emotes right
my emotes that's an extension then u
view go location that is a
extension as well those are panel
extensions
yeah can do that in Twitch
really
Bits and more. Yep. Yep. Yep. I have
Bits and Mort and everything.
There's 7TV as well. If you have the 7TV
extension install on your browser, you
can use those. Same with better Twitch
TV TTV and uh Fang Face Frerface Z as
well. Yeah, if you have those extensions
installed on browser, you can use those
emotes.
Yeah,
nice.
7TV is like a
um emote platform
which is more like a third party
extension for a streaming site like
Twitch where streamers can upload their
emotes
to 7TV and people who have viewers who
have the 7TV extension browser extension
installed on their browser They can use
these extensions and stuff.
Yeah. Oh, wait.
So, this supports YouTube and uh like
YouTube, Twitch, and Kick.
Yeah, you can have like emote sets,
etc.
Uh, wait.
If I'm correct,
wait. Um,
so this is my 7TV profile. So all these
emotes are there in
my profile thingy. Then my uploaded
emotes are here.
So people can use these uploaded ones if
they have the I have like a emote set as
well. Really nice.
Uh
when when are they going to show you uh
added YouTube connection?
I'm waiting for that.
I have one rich channel points. What
should I do? It's up to you. You can
save it and stuff. I don't have that
many um automated
uh what do you call it? Channel point
stuff which three other streamers have
right like which controls the model
which uh does things here and there. No,
I don't have those set up.
I want to in the future.
It's just that I had to minim everything
minimal for my PC setup. And even with
having everything minimal,
I'm struggling.
My PC is struggling to stream cuz
there's so many background applications
which is running to run the whole
stream.
So, it's too much. Salia
Eda there is actually I don't know if
it's okay to say this but there is
actually a modern Twitch app you can use
which I use called purple
TV
that supports like
uh 7TV
FZ fantasy face better Twitch TV etc all
those more stuff supports it even has an
ad blocker
Wait, am I allowed to say this or will I
get banned? Oh my god. So, I use purple
TV. I use purple TV sometimes.
I can You can get the download link from
Telegram, I guess. Or just search Purple
TV Twitch. You can like get it from
Oh my god.
I think I'm not supposed to say that.
Yeah.
Oh,
yeah. You know,
Oh, yeah. Speaking of uh speaking of
that um
you know um last time I uh streamed I
was like
recording like a video right how I made
my 24x7 channel thingy and the technical
details thingy. You might be wondering
Jo you recorded that 1 hour segment live
on stream. Why didn't you uploaded it?
So I thought of not uploading it because
it's over 1 hour and it's too technical.
It's too much over complicated. So I was
like what's the point of over explanate
explaining things like this? I'll just
let it be. I thought
and even today I showed a little bit of
it right how I moved everything to the
cloud
my back and stuff.
Sure. There's that.
So, I'm like, yeah, that is enough, I
guess. Now, I don't want to um over
explain too much now.
I love that I'm supposed to be studying
right now on stream and I'm like uh
talking about different things.
Oh wow.
Honestly though, I think I missed
streaming.
It's It's been It's been a while.
Yeah, it's been really a long while.
I want to be active but
yeah it's hard
cuz uh nowadays no I haven't been
playing video games I noticed that I
stopped playing Arc Raiders I I missed
my
uh I missed my expedition
second expedition I was supposed to do
it I don't know what happened but yeah
mad Marathon server slam came out,
right? Marathon the game by Bungie. Oh
my god, that I played a little bit
before it uh closed down. Tomorrow
Marathon is releasing, right? It's
2,400.
No, 2,500 rupees. O, I'm like I want to
buy it, but I'm broke right now.
Uh I can't. I've been buying supplies
and uh stuff I need for packing my stuff
since I'm leaving the country, right? Um
so I'm like I can't waste money on
buying games right now.
Let's start game streaming on April,
right? Probably April or May can expect
me to stream. I at least have to stream
four hours
um
a month or probably
uh wait
I want to check uh what is the contract
for this
uh
oh my god wait I have to check this uh
terms of service since I'm using the I'm
live streaming on this platform called
beam stream right which is sending my
Twitch and kick feed.
Uh,
right. Uh, so I have to stream at least
4 hours in a month.
If I fail to do that, I have to pay like
$10 for the premium. My sponsor thingy
or something I selected on the platform,
that will be gone.
So, I don't want that. So, I have to
wait. How do I see the terms of service?
How do I see the terms of service?
Beam stream. Oh, yeah. Beam added this
uh currency thingy called embers.
I don't think people watch me on much
people watch me on beam but
yeah I I try my best to participate in
beam beam's like giveaway stuff they
give away like like good PC stuff every
month know for channels which are doing
good they
uh yeah they give away PC for
like chance to win a PC kind of thingy.
And you need you need to like stream 4
hours for like maximum XP. Then chat
with streamers.
Uh follow channel stream on be multiream
but on four six other platforms receive
subs and gifts. You get XP. You follow
their socials. You stream from mobile
app. You stream from PlayStation.
You refer new streamers to this
platform. You get XP. refer new V
viewers. If someone subscribes, they you
get XP. Yeah, Beamstream is another
streaming platform. I'm on there. I am
there as well. Wait, let me send you
link
uh copy. Beamream uh has like a uni
chat. You can see Twitch kick YouTube uh
chat on beam.
So, which is nice.
That's why I stream on beam stream
with the multiream thingy.
Where is the uh thing?
Yeah, I'm so tired. O
streamer experience.
Uh where is this? I'm building
monetization. No viewer experience.
Doesn't say much.
Sleepy dog. Yeah.
Sleepy D.
Man, the Japanese Twitter VT Twitter is
booming with the Elgato thingy. The new
Elgato wavelength thingy. Everyone is
recommending this for VTubish. Wow.
I'm just sad that my uh saved stuff
is not
backed up. I I lost all of my stuff. Um,
yeah. So, I have to reconfigure every
single thing. O
Wait, what? Wait, what? One minute.
Stream deck. Stream Deck XL is $349.
$350.
Holy. Wait. That isn't that like how
much rupees?
Oh my god. 32,000.
Oh my god.
Wave 3 Mark 3. Mark 2. Okay. $169. Okay.
$170.
Oh.
Wave XLR MK2. H.
Wave XLR Pro. Wave XLR.
XLR dog M2. Okay. Yeah, there's like um
new Elgato gear which came out.
Man, it's so crazy, man.
I I love this one. This is the ultimate
one. Like, look.
Look at this. This is the perfect thing
you need as a YouTuber or whatever
streamer. like control a touchscreen
display of your stuff, a dial to control
your volume and other stuff, buttons to
press.
Crazy, man.
And it's expensive,
and it has a new DSP system. Oh, yeah.
This thing like inbuilt
chair processor thingy on the mic and
everything.
crazy.
So, I don't have to worry about
plugins and everything. Really nice.
Really nice. Yeah, this is the
wavelength thingy. I use it. Uh my
everything got reseted. My stuff got
reseted.
Oh, my stuff got reseted. I had like so
many applications uh like mixes here,
inputs here, mixes here. Everything was
customized.
Everything is gone now. I have to back
up somehow.
Yeah, really nice setup.
Like look, this is so good.
I can add channel audio effects, mic
level stuff, and live me stuff.
Oh,
it will be This is expensive though. Oh,
I'm probably going to save up and buy
this someday.
Yeah, but this is the ultimate thing you
need. Whether you are a video editing or
a content creator or doing anything on
your PC, you need buttons.
Yeah,
this will be nice.
output dynamic dials. Yeah, can like
control everything. You can put Chrome,
you can put OBS, Discord and stuff like
put it as a button, it will you press
the button, it will open the app
application for you. So many things,
right? Really, really, really nice if
you ask me.
Uh oh, yeah. Yeah. this thing they they
made a crossover with uh there's a
keyboard which has stream deck in it.
So the whole keyboard is customizable as
in within the software and they have a
stream deck built in. This is like the
expensive keyboard you will ever get.
Crazy.
The design is nice though, but
expensive.
Super expensive.
They released a few camera stuff as well
through facecam 4K.
Have you tried VR? I don't have a VR. I
I wish to like
have a VR stuff one day.
Oh, this is how it looks in Mac OS. The
wavelength 3.0. Oh,
there are so many. Yeah, this is the old
stream uh stream deck thingy
themes and stuff.
Really nice. Really nice.
No.
Yeah. One day. It's expensive for me.
But
it's got
one day I'll buy it.
It's a maybe though.
Yeah.
Holy god, it's two hours. Oh my god,
your boy.
I couldn't get my steady stuff done
today, but it's fine. I'll do it after
stream.
I talked a lot. I yelped a lot.
So, uh,
regarding next stream,
uh, I can try doing streams.
I don't mind doing the streams. Um,
but
it's just that I'm like too overwhelmed
with uh Japanese studies and everything
now. My brain is like ah so much stuff
and I'm when I'm on when I'm on the PC,
my brain goes multitasking mode. I'm
like, oh, I have to do this, I have to
do that. Then I'm like, "Oh, I have to
study
so much things."
So, yeah, I'll I'll I'll try to uh do at
least six streams this month.
You can count. Wait, six more than six
streams, maybe. I can't promise.
Today is the 4th of March.
Yeah, I can try to do streams. Uh don't
expect me to play video games, okay? Um
yeah, you also have a test to give,
right? Yeah. Steady, study well.
Um.
Oh yeah. So many things.
So many so many things. Mhm.
Oh yeah. I have to like send something
today. Oh yeah. To do my homework.
But yeah, I'll try to do streams here
and there. Uh, won't be gaming, but just
going to be the stalking, me yapping
about random things. Yeah, I'll schedule
it early. I'll All right.
I'll schedule it. Um, yeah. Yeah, I'll
try to schedule my streams from now on.
Um,
yeah. Uh, there are some streams which
are still in pending, right?
Oh, like the for Yeah, I accidentally
went live on the Fortnite stream today.
My bad. My bad. I had to private that
stream. Um
Um Yeah. And my whole setup only works
if I schedule YouTube streams, right? So
um I have to do that honestly.
Bash.
It's good to see that my stuff is
working. Uh I'm really excited about uh
the uh it's not that much but the
archive page is something I worked a bit
right I learned the new things
how to use GitHub actions how to use
cloudflare worker how to
AI prompt using
CLI etc so many things chip even though
it gave me the code I learned a lot by
debugging a But
ah cording is nice. Cool.
But yeah, let's hope uh um everything
goes well. Um yeah, I'm going to finish
most of my stuff by this week. Today is
Wednesday. Tomorrow is Thursday.
By this Saturday, I have to finish a lot
of things. All right. Every day time is
ticking that I can't be lazy. I can't I
I've been getting 2 hours of sleep every
day. That's why I sound so brain dead
every day these days. Holy, it's bad.
Yeah. You know, it's weird. Like 4 a.m.
like I slept at 10:00. I woke up at 2
a.m. And I was like, "Okay, I have this
crazy idea." I was like talking to Chad
GBD
like doing the doing the voice thingy
voice thingy. I was like talking, oh
yeah, I have this crazy idea. Okay, how
can I do this and that this and that?
And I was like since it's too p
uh it was too since it was too much
annoying to go upstairs and beyond PC
I started to like multitask on phone.
Oh my god it's crazy
like the thing with me is like once I
start doing something I'll go on this
tangent. It's like you are building
something
like for example if I were to say an
example I'm like okay I'm going to do a
stream today I'm going to play a game or
something right and in that game I'm
going to specifically win the match
right kind of that was my goal initial
goal then I'll be uh like doing the goal
but also improving that goal or like
doing something else making it more uh
advanced or whatever like doing
challenges in between to and finally
winning the match or something like I
don't know if it was a good example. So
basically that I keep on
uh one idea I keep on improving that
idea over time and then I get the final
result and I'm like okay good if if it
it works it's nice
stuff like that. Yeah. But yeah anyway
uh it is going to be 6:30.
It's going to be 6:30. Yeah. Yeah, I
will I'll wrap up soon.
I'll wrap up soon, have dinner early and
start revision, homework, all those
stuff.
Yeah, I'll just do that.
But yeah, it's good to uh uh stream here
and there.
But yeah, I I want to say thank you to
all who actually came by today. Um,
it really means a lot. I didn't expect
anyone to show cuz I felt like I haven't
shown myself for like four or five weeks
and maybe people forgot. Maybe they
won't get notified.
But I'm really thankful that
you guys came by today and chatted with
me. It really from the bottom of my
heart, it really means a lot. So yeah,
thank you.
Uh wait, I just clicked on the surot
emote.
Uh and it says subscribe to get the
emote. Oh, that's like a surbot uh uh
emote. No, for people
uh
who use on on Twitch, if you see emotes
sp like sent by other people, those own
specific like that emote have belongs to
a channel, right? For example, since you
are a subscriber on my channel, that
means you can use this emote in anywhere
on Twitch.
Whoever you watch, you can you can send
this jock warm hearts emote, etc. Uh
yeah, you can use that on anywhere on
Twitch, right? Since you're a
subscriber, right? Same thing. If other
people want to use that emote, they have
to subscribe to that specific channel
like that. Same thing, same logic.
On YouTube, it's like you can't use
other channels emotes anywhere else
globally.
on YouTube. It's like you
apply for a membership for a channel and
you can only use it on that specific
channel kind of thingy, right? Yeah.
Same thing on kick. Uh same thing as
YouTube. You can use the emotes globally
if you're a subscriber on kick. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. It's really nice.
show that you
Hi.
Okay. Uh where's my uh let me open this
up. I'll redirect you to my W channel.
All right. Uh I just closed my OBS. Uh
since I'm running Mel, right? Mel takes
so much CPU, man. My PC is not handling
when I'm streaming with Mel. Um, so
yeah, let me open OBS and get the watch
channel running. Um, I don't have it um
cloud-based thingy, the watch channel
stuff. One day I'll do it.
But yeah, uh, it should be
stream number 19, right? Playlist. Okay,
let me see.
Okay.
Okay. I'll go live now. Okay. Nice.
Okay. I'll redirect you guys to my
uh V channel. Okay.
Well, I may have to leave. Uh hope it
was fun chatting. Yeah. Chatting. Yes.
Thank you. I like Bagley. Did I miss
something? No. Uh yeah, I'm wrapping up
the stream.
I'm wrapping up the stream in a kiss. We
were just talking about stuff. Don't
worry much.
Um, yeah. Yeah, it's uh 2 hours now. I'm
going to take a bath.
Freshen up and go study. Got homework to
do.
Yeah,
crazy.
But yeah, don't worry. I'll try to
stream tomorrow or like uh this week
I'll try to do at least two streams.
Count this as number first the stream
number one.
Yeah, but don't expect uh talk to me.
Okay, fine. I'll stay for a little bit.
Fine.
Uh uh wait, how many hours is it?
2 hours. Okay, 15 minutes. I'll stay for
15 minutes. I'll make it 2 hour 30
minutes. Okay.
Okay. 2 hour 30 minutes. You get 50
minutes. Fine.
It's not like
Hi.
Okay.
We'll do it like that.
So, yeah. How is How are you doing? It's
been a while, right?
How is life,
bro? I'm bad at making conversations.
Yeah, it's been a while, too. Hi.
Bye-bye. AB, thank you for dropping by.
Have a good evening ahead. Good luck.
So, when are you leaving? How many more
days? Uh, end of this month.
I'm leaving by
29th or 30th or 31st. Not confirmed.
Uh but by April I'll be
uh I'm I'm not in India anymore. Uh
I have exams coming on Sunday right
15th. So I have to study for the exam.
After exams it's going to be speedun
packing packing packing everything.
Packing up things this and that etc.
Yeah,
crazy.
By the way, by the way,
I'll give the Twitch tab here cuz auto
mode happens. Now, I don't even get
notified.
Uh
okay.
On screen keyboard. I can close that.
House manager. Uh
today was the opening day of our new
club called inter international
relations student club. Ooh,
that sounds fun. I'm one of the founding
member. Oh, nice.
Let's go.
What do you do in this club? Tell me.
I'm a I'm curious. What do you do in
this club?
International relation.
Wait. Relation or real? Wait.
relation as in you talk like you connect
with people and like talk about life or
something. How is this about
student club
student clubs?
That is so nice.
Student clubs and stuff
must be nice.
H. Oh, what is this on YouTube? Shopping
tag products. Oh, I can put products.
Wait, I see Flipkart like the Oh, wait.
I can like What?
I can products.
Wait, how does this work?
YouTube shopping. Huh?
Wait, can I like look for
Wait, how does this work? Wait,
if I click on this,
let me click on a good item.
I add it.
Create a product drop. What is this?
Well, I earn commission. What is this?
It
crazy.
Oh,
so ex international student didn't have
any club and we were badly ignored in
our university but now we have one. So
basically everything supporting students
helping them cultures and festival
celebrations and international
collaborations and also other with other
clubs and at universities.
Wow, that sounds so cool.
Clubs and stuff. Nah.
Wow,
that sounds so cool.
That sounds so nice. H I wonder if I'll
also have clubs for my um
university and also language school.
Probably I'll have clubs I guess cuz
probably yeah it has to be Yeah, they
have like club system, right?
Yeah, I guess that Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
True. True. Yeah,
that's so nice.
Yeah.
So, if technically your club president,
right, cuz you're a founding member
like just like in the anime and stuff,
you have your own club room. uh you have
you you'll be like discussing
uh stuff plans and activities with your
club members
and like uh when there's a club
exhibition show like a cultural festival
or something you you will take um your
club also has to do stuff right
preparing talking with clubmates
bonding oh my god that was fun it's like
Um
this reminds me of extracurricular PTP
periods or something. I think in high
school I had club thingy. There's like
few things to choose now like chess
club, music club,
um
yeah indoors and outdoors. There's
football club, basketball club, table
tennis club,
uh volleyball club, all those stuff
right in high school. I remember that.
So similar to like Oh my god.
Oh nice,
bro. That was so so good.
We had to work a lot as we doing
everything by Yeah. Yeah. True, true,
true. Yes,
that is true.
That is true. Yeah.
Sounds fun though. really really sounds
fun.
Really, really sounds fun.
I just hope I can stream man and talk
about things in life
uh when I'm there next month, right?
I'll have a I'll have a roommate. So I
don't know if I can yap stuff openly
like this cuz roommate will be in my
room like in our in my dom room and
he'll be just watching me yap and talk
right if I doing streams or something.
Another thing I can do is I can go to a
cafe and do but public space now that
will be too much to do live streams. I
can go out and um
I can I can go out and like uh do work
stuff. Yeah.
What about you telling me something new?
There's nothing much new. Uh basically
I've been preparing for my stuff.
uh been wanting to stream, but
I've been holding back from streaming
here and there cuz um it's not good to
stream if you're like too tired and dead
inside, right?
Um that's like low energy levels, right?
Back in the days, I would do anything to
stream. like if I'm feeling depressed,
sad, uh or happy, any emotions, if I
stream, I'll be happy. Adrenaline kicks
in, all those stuff. Nowadays, I don't
know what happened. Uh maybe life is
hitting me or something. Or maybe like
the uh the the pressure of streaming or
uh things I um
see uh like how do I say it? Yeah, back
when I was stream uh seeing this as a
hobby and a fun thing to do for time
pass or like when I'm bored. Uh yeah, I
didn't care much about things. Now I'm
like starting to care about oh I have to
make it more I have to put effort this
and that and I'm like uh so brain deaded
every day like doing stuff going out
etc. And I'm like, "Ah,
do I need to stream?" And I just uh
think about streaming and I sleep off. I
wake up and I'm like, "Ah, I missed.
Next day I'll be like, "Okay, next day
I'll stream."
That's my everyday
skin color-wise. I can't say that. I
can't say that. I mean, yeah, let it be
your imagination, I guess.
But yeah,
I I think I'm brown color like brown or
lighter brown. I don't know.
Who knows? Does it matter?
Skin color doesn't matter. No.
Um I'm the only one on stream. There's a
reason I'm asking. Hi
I got you,
man. Streams have been I need a stream
more.
But honestly, I
uh then initially it'll be freaking
lonely as people won't be interacting.
You don't know good enough Japanese to
talk for. Yeah, true.
Oh god,
it's going to be rough now.
Oh yeah, it's going to be rough
from next month onwards.
Wow, it's going to be rough.
Like at least I hope I can just uh be on
Discord VC or some thing or just talk
with people, you know. um when I'm
there. Um
I have to I I just cut out the times and
everything
uh like when I could
talk uh with people and I could go out
when I have to do this.
So yeah, April will be like a month for
me where I'll be scouting out and
writing, taking notes, memos
like okay, this is the time period I can
be free. I will have to plan things out,
right?
Yeah. So many things.
I'll probably be releasing a video
talking about
like what what do you call it? talking
about my moving to Japan thingy, I
guess. Final video.
I recorded my house.
But you know what? Honestly speaking,
no.
I feel like the only thing I regret is
the only thing I regret is publicly
announcing and mentioning that I'm going
uh to Japan like this, right?
I I I think if I could if if I could go
back in time, I would
honestly just scold myself and not like
um remind myself do not you don't need
to publicly open up things to the public
and stuff, right? Yeah. I think that's
the only thing I I regret.
Uh other than that, it's all good. Like
normally
what's wrong with it? A lot of things
have been wrong with it.
So many things happened. Uh
yeah, so many things. Oh god. 2025 was a
rough year for me.
Yeah.
Uh so many things, right? Competition
thingy
this and that.
Uh h
doxing all those stuff this and that
whatever happened.
Yeah, it's scary man. I I was so dumb. I
uh didn't think much about it. Now I
understand the complications, right? If
you're a content creator or like someone
who is out there in the internet talking
about your stuff, you have to protect
your privacy, this and that. I could
have just revealed it like casually out
of nowhere, drop a video or just an
announcement. Oh, I'm moving to Japan.
Bye. And no one would even uh
like they'll be like surprised and
happy. Yeah, that's it. But if I uh keep
on talking about it, my excitement and
stuff, I mean it's fine.
But yeah, I I had some good good
experience and bad experience. That's
why I mentioned that.
Yeah, you know, your online privacy, you
have to like Yeah, be careful about it.
I've been like super careless with it
and I learned it the hard way like Yeah.
Yeah, bro. If you do this, you're going
to suffer.
My uh crazy.
You got me as a good thing. Best reader.
We new best viewer.
Yeah, that's what I said. Like there are
good there are good. Uh there's pros and
cons. No
m.
But that's about it.
Rosen
it in each one though like to just
casually talk and everything
and uh one other thing is now I tend to
what's it called? Uh there's this
thing right. Um let me Google this
selfinssert
meaning uh
where other versions of them. Oh yeah.
Yeah. So I think sometimes I selfinsert
myself
right with my tubing thingy as in
um
as in like I talk about my life
everything
more like open open normally you're
supposed to play a character and uh not
supposed to break the emotion and
everything I I'm doing that normal
streamer
with 3.
So I have to be uh kind of careful here
and there. That's what I learned. But
it's all right too. So yeah,
the thing with me now, I get scolded a
lot. Like I once I open my mouth, I'm
super open.
You know, I want like if if there's
something which is supposed to be a
secret, I accidentally unconsciously
reveal it, I'm like, "Oh, hey, why can't
I shut up about it? It's supposed to be
a secret."
Yeah. So, that's why I have to be super
um careful. Hi, thank you for the stop
over thinging thingy.
Hi.
really nice. Mhm. So, yeah, I'll try to
do more streams. Um,
just casual chatting, you know, cuz
again, I won't get to chat with everyone
like this
next Monday.
So,
I'm going to do couple more streams.
We talk. It will be really nice if you
can come by. I promise I will. Uh, no, I
don't I don't want to promise, but keep
an eye for schedule streams. Okay, I'll
somehow make it so that whenever I
schedule a stream on YouTube, it
automatically
shows up on Twitch like the Twitch
schedule thingy, right? On channels.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So, it will take the
title and the category. I think I can
keep like a null something. I don't
know. Let's see if I can make it happen.
Allows chat GPT.
Um, allows chat GPT. Like, can I
uh can I do this automated? Wink wink
then like um
yeah, set it up in CloudFare Worker.
Yeah,
man. I'm addicted to Cloudfare worker
and GitHub actions and everything.
Someone stopped me. Like, bro, ever
since I discovered this, I'm like, what
is this? This is so cool.
I don't need to use Sammy. I don't have
to turn my PC on and do everything,
automation thingy, everything. Um, like
do it manually. I can just like line of
code, it will do it. Super crazy, man.
and I nerd out when I talk about tech
stuff.
So, but yeah,
so yeah, I'm really happy uh about the
archive page I made uh recently.
I hope you guys will like it. Um
oh, uh let me explain. One second. Um
wait, uh
one second. One second. Let me open
these. Um
and da
this is like too extra extra but not
needed. One second. Uh Twitch
archive job. Next. Okay, that one and
GitHub uh
worker
build. Okay, let me show you
switch.
Okay, so uh last time I developed so
stuff so many stuff in Sammy, right?
Streamerboard Sammy like this YouTube
API buttons, Discord buttons, etc.,
etc., right? I had like uh files this
and that right so many things right
locally in my computer but since I'm
going next month I can't do a normal
YouTube stream
if everything is broken broken right if
I don't have this application it is it
won't work right I mean it will work but
like um announcements won't be automated
uh going live tweets uh like
announcement will not be automated. So
many breaking right. So I realized I
could use cloudfare worker.
I have a discord engine. This is this
runs every 10 minutes. So this is the
one which is uh taking care of the
discord stuff like announcement when I'm
live on YouTube, Twitch, all those
stuff. And it automatically creates
events, right? All those stuff. Same
thing I did it did here. Um I replicated
it in the cloud and then I have the I
have to do the what thingy the 24x
channel stuff right I have to do that
later. Then I have a stream uh API
thingy that are uh makes this website.
So every stream I do there is a entry.
So you can see all these uh full details
except analytics.
Uh let me show you one second.
Uh let it load. Yeah. So you can watch
the stream like this was my last stream
on YouTube, right? Can watch the stream.
You can see the details of when did the
stream was when was the stream
scheduled? When did the stream go live?
When did it end? You can see the
description if you need description. You
can see the transcript. Yes, this
transcript. You can see the whole
transcript.
And uh you can see the live chat. See,
YouTube chat is here. Everyone from
YouTube is here.
Okay. Wait, there's an ad break. Wait,
let's wait. Um,
you ced these on Cloud? Yeah, I did it.
I did that on CloudFare.
Yeah, yeah. Uh, wait, let's wait for uh
Wait, there's an ad break right on
Twitch.
And there's AI summary as well.
Uh, it summarizes what the stream was
about and the uh timestamps are here.
You know coding? Nope. I do not know
coding. I just asked Chip PT, hey, I
have this crazy idea. You don't get ads.
Okay, good. I don't have I don't I have
this crazy idea. I want to do this and
this and this like that. So, I did it in
CloudFare and then I have a GitHub repo
which has all my YouTube data. So, the
AI generated stuff for each streams are
here.
Uh like all the timestamps and
everything for each video is here. The
subtitles for each video
is here. Like all the video and its
subtitles are here. English, Japanese,
um
English, Japanese, everything. And I
have my thumbnails folder. Every 115
streams I have done in my YouTube
channel, all of their thumbnails are
here. See?
So I use cloudf to fetch the data from
here and like do it everything
automated. Yes. Hello dragoner.
Good evening. Happy holy.
Then I have like a timeline stuff. This
has like uh the YouTube chat and the
subtitle. Yeah. So in the archive page
when you click YouTube live replay
you'll see the chats with the with the
transcript.
Yeah. Yeah. Mhm. So uh a good example
will be this stream the valerent stream
I did last time. So I can put manual
entry
a manual entry as in stream summary.
This is what I will write from notion.
This is what I'll write from notion
manually. For example, uh yeah, streams,
right? Um Valerant. Yeah. So, I can
write stuff here like stuff here. Go
here. Refresh the page.
Wait for it. See, it shows up. See, it's
easy. Like now um one thing I'm going to
do after this stream is I'm going to
uh make a thing where it says community
contributions. So if someone followed
me, if someone donated uh something to
me, etc. Those credits will be here. So
you can see, oh, Z did this stream,
Valerin stream on January 13th. And
these were the people who donated,
followed, subscribed, etc. And these are
the time. Yeah, I got to make it. So you
click on the time and it will uh the
player like player head. No, when you
click on it, it will uh go to 2 minute
like that. Yeah. And it also has Billy
Billy thingy. Whenever this stream is
uploaded on Billy Billy,
uh that preview will be here, etc.
So cool, right? And uh if I send this on
uh Twitter
x.com, if I send this on Twitter, it
will also uh I put the metadata stuff as
well.
If I send this on Twitter, right, I have
the metadata. See, it's a large some uh
card with the title from my website. You
click on it get shown to this. So yeah,
so I don't have to write tweets, right?
Today was a fun stream. We did this and
that and this and that. I don't need to
write it. I can just link my page easy.
No.
Yeah, it's it's crazy but too much
complicated. But yeah, I made it
existent.
Yeah. But yeah, this is more like an
archive for people if you want.
Yeah. Yeah. This is today's stream. This
current stream what we are doing today.
Yeah, archive is here. Once this stream
is processed, once we have the subtitle
after four or 2 hours or 3 hours, my
GitHub stuff,
I have this GitHub stuff. These are the
workers. This will automatically trigger
every 1 hour, every 30 minutes, every 6
hour. The AI stuff will happen every 6
hour. So uh once the YouTube streamer is
processed the AI worker will generate
the metadata
the summary timestamps and the
description for the website. Then yeah
all these things etc. So yeah,
thumbnails, streams, playlist and for
Twitch people,
I will be
linking the YouTube uh like Twitch chat.
No, for people on Twitch,
your chat will be here like there will
be a section view Twitch live chat
replay. You click on it, you see your
Twitch chat
uh like yeah avatar username message.
There will be emoji render rendering as
well. You know Twitch emotes, right?
So that will be there. So yeah, really
nice, right?
Really nice. More like an archive page.
Not needed, but I just made it.
So, and also I can show you this uh for
the V war channel right
for the V channel I I made some systems
here.
So uh in the f far future
instead of running this on OBS
it will automatically detect that I am
live on YouTube twitch kick and stuff
and I can set the live board so people
will see a post uh playback and they
will see the schedule
and uh there'll be like fan arts and
everything people who made fan arts for
me all throughout this year like uh all
these years they'll see fan arts, you'll
see background music, everything all
within the website itself. Yeah. Yeah.
And all it shows the schedule for the
streams and everything. So if it's
playing Hongkey star rail, it'll be
number it's it's broken, but yeah, it's
number two. It's supposed to be f uh
yeah, it's five like that. Everything
it's like obviously no. And uh back how
do I change it back? Okay, so I have to
do
uh wait a minute. Uh
what's the command? I forgot. Oh boy, I
forgot. Wait,
wait, what's the command? Oh, wait. Oh.
Oh, no. Wait.
Yeah, rerun mode will be the full
screen. Yeah.
So, I don't need to use uh OBS scenes,
etc.
Isn't it so cool? I did so much.
Oh, my PC is lagging. Oh,
yeah. Yeah, I did so much.
Ah, really nice.
Oh my god.
cuz yeah stuff like that
cuz every time I get idea now I'm like I
want to do this I want to do that
how can I improve this
so that's what I do it
I don't know if it's good but yeah too
much technical no but it's nice though
everything is automated
God, I love this.
But I I wish I knew coding, man. I show
signs that
I I show signs of being a this tech nerd
guy or something who knows coding and
this and that, but I little do you know
I know nothing. I do not know HTML how
to do HTML CSS nothing.
I just ask watch YouTube tutorials
understand oh this is what is this and
then I try to do it that's why my
website stuff too like it's really bad
cuz I don't know CSS so much stuff I
could improve it right
but yeah one day
one day
yeah my idea my thing is like If there
was a way to automate everything,
my day-to-day workflow, then it's easier
for me, right? I have less stress.
Uh don't need to worry about stuff.
Everything will be done, right?
Yeah.
So nice.
Wow. I bet you'll be stuck one day.
I wish though.
Yeah, I I don't know why I'm smiling so
much when I talk about these, but yeah,
it's kind of boring to listen to and
super confusing. Uh cuz I I the thing is
now with me
uh people like me, we I tend to or we
tend there are people like me who tend
to overexlain, right? People won't
listen to that over explanation, right?
Unless you know what the person is
talking about, they'll listen. For the
like an ordinary person, they will skim
through it and will like to have like
TLDDR stuff, right? Yeah. That's also
one of the reason why I didn't upload
that technical details video. I was
like, yeah, 2our long yapping about some
stuff. Why?
It is simple. Don't need to do that.
But uh really nice
so many things.
Thank good
you are inspiration. Really?
Yeah. I wish I was this inspir like uh
invested into stuff like stud like if I
was this into like tech stuff. No, I
wish I could show that in music stuff or
even language stuff as well like
speaking even for uh singing extra extra
too like I wish I was this into it. No,
especially for music, man. Music is
something my childhood dream and I'm not
even doing anything anything revolving
music nowadays.
I'm like, I'll do it later later.
Yeah, I also need to do this for music
now. Yeah, hope I can do it next month.
Like, yeah, I'll adjust time.
I I'll mainly focus on music production
stuff.
You're not sticking to it. Yeah, true,
true, true.
I'm still in that process of finding
myself now. What is the thing? What is
my niche? What is what is it that I like
to do?
Yeah,
really nice.
Let me drink some water.
Yeah. So many things.
You can
I'm fine with selling myself services,
but
unless and until I'm good enough
because the thing with me, you know, I'm
too much of a perfectionalist
sadly.
So
yeah, I I would like to do it only if
I'm good enough, like I have good
potential etc.
And if I can make my customer happy and
they get to see a finished a good
finished product something from me then
only I'll let let them do yeah
pay me or something cuz who like I don't
want to be like those GFX bots right
which tried to uh make you commission
them like those scam bots artist bots
come to your streams and u tell you they
can do stuff for you and etc. And they
give you a bad product and you're like,
"Ah, my money's worth. This is not my
money's worth. I got scammed. I don't
want that." No.
Yeah.
That's the thing with
being a perfectionist is bad. I guess
my is
I I would like them.
I have so much ideas in my mind. The
thing is now uh every day I'm bringing
new ideas to my own plate which is
already full and I'm like bro I have
exam coming. I have to pack stuff. I
have to reset my PC,
clean out stuff, add stuff to Google
Drive, but like buy, you know, use my
SSD and like sort out stuff, delete
unwanted files from like back in the
days like downloads from back in the
days, unwanted stuff, plugins, music
stuff,
um,
programs, data, everything. backups I
don't need. I have to clean out my whole
PC
in like a week
and I'm like, "Oh, do this, do that,
etc."
Crazy.
I I'll tell you probably what I'm going
to do. Okay. After the stream, I'll be
charging the Twitch linking thingy. like
how can I link a Twitch stream which I
did to the YouTube ID YouTube thingy the
data thingy I made right that stuff then
I'll be like oh finally it works then
I'm going to do kick then I'm going to
figure out how to get kick chat as a
JSON file so I can put it in the website
now so people can see YouTube Twitch
kick chat when they see the archive page
and stuff etc etc
and then I'm like having ideas like um I
used to have a collaborator
database system
uh which could be nice for my archive
page like if I'm doing a collab with a
content creator right their data
everything will be in a saved in a
database right like their YouTube
channel Twitch channel uh socials
their username, their PGs, etc., right?
That'll be saved in a database. So, it
can like be like, yeah, Jo collabed with
at creator and it'll pull the data and
it will show it on the website. Like
when you open the stream, they'll be
like, "Oh, this was a collaboration
stream." Here you can see the collab
partners social media. If you want to
support this creator, the collaborator,
you can click on their links like that,
like a call CTA, call to action button
or something. Really nice, right?
Yeah. I was like 4:00 a.m. in the
morning. I was like brainstorming these
ideas and everything
and I'm like, "Okay, I'm not going to be
collabing anytime soon with anyone
or doing any collabs or something, so
what's the point?"
God, I need to stop. I I need to stop.
My brain is like
on de like a a developer mode or
something.
But all of this is for a stream thingy,
you know, for me tubing, something I'm
passionate about.
So
it is nice, right? When you look at it
this way, like, oh, I'm doing stuff for
my own
uh convenience. No, not convenience,
more quality of life thingy, right?
H rather than a basic uh as a content
graduate you have to worry about posting
on multiple platforms
make announcements this and that this
and that and here I am automating
everything
and doing extra extra unnecessary
stuffhu
but yeah kind of nice
cuz I want to do it so I'm doing
We try to Instagram at least once a
week. Yeah, I'll try. The thing is now I
don't use much Instagram and other
places.
Yeah,
I I barely even know what's going on in
the internet nowadays.
All I'm doing is like, okay, what I got
to I listen to music.
Telegram. I don't use Telegram. I used
to We We used to have a Telegram
uh broadcast channel or like a group or
something
uh where I post notifications whenever
I'm live and everything, right? I used
to do that. I had a WhatsApp group uh
broadcast channel.
that channel thing you know not the
group group WhatsApp channel telegram
channel all those stuff I had
so whenever I'm live there used to be
like a announcement but but the thing
was now I had to manually do it now
cuz I didn't know how uh I didn't know
you can go with like WhatsApp board
telegram board and stuff to automate it
uh I was like ah I don't know how to do
it I don't want to do it kind of
But now I create chajipity.
Yeah, I can be like help me chip. I want
to do this, automate this. It'll give me
ideas and give me code. I do this that
nice.
I think it's too much.
Too much.
Anyhow, we talked about tech stuff. I
noted out.
I missed the streaming man.
Yeah.
H It's 3 hours. We have to wrap up. Oh,
it's 700. I got to eat dinner.
freshen up, do homework, go to sleep,
wake up at 6, uh wake up at 4:00,
revise, attend my classes, and and maybe
I'll stream
um in the morning. Oh, yeah. Since I'm
waking up at since I have morning
classes
at 6 uh 30 and stuff,
I could technically
uh
do morning streams at 10:00 a.m. maybe.
Or would you prefer like evening like
around this like 4:00 p.m. 5:00 p.m.?
I could try.
Yeah,
let me hear you more.
A thank you. It makes me happy that I
want me to you want to hear me talk and
yap.
But yeah, I have to go.
Okay, let me check my schedule.
Today's 4. Okay, tomorrow I think I can
do a stream. I want to marry you
someday.
What?
I can't stop laughing. Oh yeah.
Um, okay. Tomorrow we'll do stream. I'll
try to do streams. Okay.
Uh, tomorrow we'll do streams
and
expect no game streams. Expect uh
chatting stream like this mainly or or
or uh steady stream or like work with me
stream. Maybe I'll work my all these
stuff I'm doing in the back while I'm
yapping all my brains out narrating what
I'm doing. Uh maybe I'll I'll not show
it on screen cuz it's too technical and
boring. I'll just Yap yap. Uh you will
just see like a lowfi music and this
background I guess.
Uh yeah. And uh and maybe I haven't
practiced singing and all those stuff in
a while. So I'll just maybe I'll one day
one of these days I'll do that. God I'm
bad at singing but still I'll learn
stuff. It's been a while now.
I have to do something at least. Yeah, I
mainly expect chatting streams like
this. I would love to chat with
everyone. Uh it would mean a lot if you
could come by. Um, I'll not do uh
unexpected streams anymore. I'll just
schedule it early. If there's any delay
with the stream, I'll tweet it out or
mention in the chats of the stream.
Okay. So, don't worry. Hey,
I'll wrap up. Wait.
Oh, yeah. I have to make the automation,
right? So when I end my stream, it will
automatically
raid my
24x7 channel. Ah,
and automatically pin them. Oh, wait. I
don't think Twitch allows you to pin via
API. Ah, it's okay. I'll figure it out.
What am I doing? I My brain just lagged.
Oh, end stream. Oh, yeah.
Oh, god. Hi. Hi. Hi.
Let me
am I live on the other? Okay, I'm live.
Hi,
don't cry.
I'll be there tomorrow probably. Yeah,
I'll try my best to be there tomorrow.
Don't worry.
Hi.
Does it work? Okay, it works. Hi. Thank
you to all. Where is my OBS? Oh, wait.
It's lagging. It's lagging. It's
lagging. Oh, god.
No, it's lagging. Don't like it. Don't
lag. Am I Am I lying? Oh. Oh. Oh.
Busy.
Okay.
Hi. Uh,
ending stream.
So, thank you to all who came by today
on YouTube and Twitch and Kick and Beam
at all these platforms. Thank you so so
much. I'll see you tomorrow for the next
stream.
It really means a lot from a bottom of
my heart that people came by and talked
with me. I expected no one to show up
actually cuz it's been a while, right?
People forgot about me or something cuz
I was busy with life. But yeah, thank
you for taking your a moment of your
time and spending it with me. Thank you
so much and do have a good good evening
ahead, evening, morning, whatever the
time it is for you. Do have a good day
ahead.
Don't forget to do your do good deeds of
today and have fun.
I'm going to wrap it up here. Hi, this
was Ch Next.
Bye-bye.